# Fatemeh Ghasemikoli

#### FRONT WEB DEVELOPMENT

f.ghasemi33@gmail.com Irvine, California, 92620-2130 f.ghasemi33@gmail.com 9493009064

Enthusiastic and task-driven professional with experience in web programming and development. Clear understanding of coding, troubleshooting, developing databases, and creating user interfaces. Success in leading teams and providing training support for new team members. Familiar with Java Script, React, CSS, and HTML languages. Motivated to learn, grow, and excel as a front-end web developer.

## **Key Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- lava Script
- React
- Git

## **Professional Experience**

Leadership Team Member Oakley | March 2016 - December 2020

- Managed team of individuals in the Oakley Custom Program (OCP) department.
- Mentored and guided employees to foster proper completion of assigned duties.
- Demonstrated knowledge of company mission and goals and mentored employees in reaching objectives aligned with company core values.
- Facilitated training for associates through daily coaching and regular performance appraisals.
- Working through SAP software and prepare routine tasks
- Checked inventory on SAP software and adjusted accordingly to ensure proper inventory was reflected.
- Delivered training support and management to team while completing daily tasks.
- Managed online orders and prepared order shipments.
- Championed a special project focused on improving productivity, leading to 20% increases in the department
- Improved department efficiency by three days per week by combining inventory management with daily tasks.

#### Front-End Developer

ESANJ | January 2014 - March 2016

- Assembled and addressed technical and design requirements, integrating user-facing and front-end elements to maintain web presence effectiveness.
- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- · Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- · Delivered responsive web design projects in Agile framework.
- Handled design, development, deployment and maintenance of integration processes.
- Researched and proposed new solutions to make website more user-friendly.
- Discussed site and app requirements with clients to produce actionable development plans.

### **Education**

Bachelor Degree in Software Engineer Abrar University at Iran | September 2011 - July 2013

Associate Degree in Computer Science SaddleBack college at Mission Viejo, California | January 2020 - May 2023

Certificate in Web Development Udemy | October 2021 - March 2022